Johnson, Lawrence R. Missouri Pacific Railroad and Railroad Union Publications 6330 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- United Transportation Union, Other Unions, and Missouri Pacific Railroad, Publication (Box 2)
  - BLF&E Ritual of B of LF & E 1945, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Capital Lodge #622, 1944; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - United Railroad Operating Crafts By-Laws 1951, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: By-Laws of United Railroad Operating Crafts, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Iron Workers. Constitution 1956, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: Constitution of the International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental Iron Workers, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Agreements 1952-1974 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Missouri Pacific Railroad Company, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Item 2: Single Seniority Agreement Effective June 1, 1974 between Missouri Pacific Railroad and United Transportation Union (T&C), Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Air Brakes 1958-1975 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Missouri Pacific Railroad System Lines, 1975; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Item 2: Missouri Pacific Railroad Company Maintenance and Operation of Air Brake, Air Signal, Steam Heat and Air Conditioning Equipment, and Train Handling Instructions, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Item 3: Maintenance and Operation of Air and Dynamic Brakes, Air Signal and Train Handling Instructions, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Item 4: Missouri-Illinois Railroad New Orleans Lower Coast Railroad, 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Circular No. 7 1959, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Circular No. 21-C, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: Circular No. 21-C, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Circular No. 81 1945-1980 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Circular No. 81, 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Item 2: Circular No. 81, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Item 3: Circular No. 81, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Item 4: Circular No. 81, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Caboose Form Packet, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: 24-A Report of Highway Crossing Accident, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 2: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 3: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 4: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 5: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 6: Report of All Personal Injuries and All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 7: Report of All Personal Injuries and All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 8: Conductor's Hot Box Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 9: Report of Work Train Service or Pilot Service, or Pilot Service for Maintenance of Way Equipment, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 10: Cars Picked Up Without A Work Order, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 11: Report of All Personal Injuries and All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 12: Report of All Personal Injuries And All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 13: Report of All Personal Injuries and all Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 14: Cars Picked Up Without A Work Order, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 15: Report of Work Train Service, or Pilot Service for Maintenance of Way Equipment, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 16: Conductor's Hot Box Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 17: Missouri Pacific Railroad Company and Subsidiaries, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 18: Report of All Personal Injuries and All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 19: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 20: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 21: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 22: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 23: 24-A Report of Highway Crossing Accident, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 24: Missouri Pacific Railroad Company and Subsidiaries, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 25: Conductor's Hot Box Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 26: 24-A Report of Highway Crossing Accident, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 27: Cars Picked Up Without A Work Order, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 28: Cars Picked Up Without A Work Order, 1978; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 29: Report of All Personal Injuries and All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 30: Report of All Personal Injuries and All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 31: Report of Work Train Service, or Pilot Service for Maintenance of Way Equipment, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 32: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 33: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 34: 705 Report, 1976; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 35: Report of All Personal Injuries and All Crossing Accidents, 1972; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Item 36: Caboose Condition Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Health Plans 1984-1991 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Your Health Care Plan Retirees, 1991; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Item 2: Your Health Care Plan, 1989; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Item 3: 1989 Affliated Health Providers, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Item 4: Your Health Care Plan: The Members' Handbook, 1984; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Hospital Association 1948-1968 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Circular No. 1, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Item 2: Constitution and By-Laws, 1954; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Item 3: Constitution and By-Laws, 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Item 4: Constitution and By-Laws, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Item 5: Rules and Regulations, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Hours of Service Act. 1946, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Hours of Service Act, 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Item 2: Hours of Service Act, 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Illinois Division Safety Sentinel, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: Illinois Division Safety Sentinel, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Item 2: Illinois Division Safety Sentinel, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. MPEHA News 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: M.P.E.H.A. News, 1988; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Item 2: M.P.E.H.A News, 1988; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Item 3: M.P.E.H.A. News, 1986; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Maintenance of Way and Structures 1929, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Rules and Instructions for the Maintenance of Way and Structures, 1929; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Operating Rules 1950, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: The Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Item 2: Giving An Analysis Of Rule 99 And Rule 93, 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Item 3: Questionnaire on Supplement to The Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Operating Rules 1968, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Item 1: Catechism on the Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Item 2: Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Item 3: Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Operating Rules 1968, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Item 1: Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Item 2: Uniform Code of Operating Rules, 1968; Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Operating Rules Examination 1982, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Item 1: Operating Employees' Rules Class, 1982; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Radio Communication 1968-1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Item 1: Rules and Instructions Governing the Operation of a Railroad Radio Communication System, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Rules Education Pamphlet, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Item 1: Uniform Code Railroads Rules Educational Pamphlet, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Safety 1941-1977 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Item 1: Safety Rules, 1941; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Item 2: Our Safety Plan, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Item 3: Think Practice Talk Your Safety, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Item 4: Charts Prepared from D.O.T. Regulations for Transportation of Explosives and Other Dangerous Articles by Freight, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Item 5: Uniform Code of Safety Rules, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Item 6: Uniform Code of Safety Rules, 1971; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Item 7: Giving An Analysis Of Rules Provifing Safety At The Meeting Point, 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Schedules of Wages, 1924-1953 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Item 1: Schedule of Wages Trainmen, 1924; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Item 2: Schedule of Wages Trainmen, 1934; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Item 3: Schedule of Wages Yardmen, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Item 4: Schedule of Wages Trainmen, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Item 5: Schedule of Wages Conductors, 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Item 6: Schedule of Wages Trainmen, 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Schedules of Wages 1961, Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Item 1: Special Agreements, Ruling and Interpretations, Changes in Schedules of Wages, 1956; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Schedules of Wages Conductors and Trainmen 1970, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Item 1: Schedule of Pay Allowed and Rules Governing Conductors and Trainmen, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Item 2: Schedule of Pay Allowed and Rules Governing Conductors and Trainmen, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Schedules of Wages Conductors and Trainmen 1970, Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Item 1: Schedule of Pay Alloweed and Rules Governing Conductors and Trainmen, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Item 2: Schedules of Pay Allowed and Rules Governing Conductors and Trainmen, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Item 3: Schedules of Wages Yardmen, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Item 4: Schedules of Wages Yardmen, 1970; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Schedules of Wages Yardmen 1970, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Special Instruction's 1940-1950 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Item 1: Eastern Division, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Item 2: Kansas City Terminal Division, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Item 3: Eastern Division, 1940; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Item 4: St. Louis Terminal Division Timetable No. 34, 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Item 5: Eastern Division Special Instructions No. 1, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Timetables 1959, Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Item 1: General Notice No. 15, 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Timetable 1966, Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Item 1: Timetable No. 1, 1966; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Timetables 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Item 1: System Timetable No. 9, 1977; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Item 2: System Timetable No. 13, 1979; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Timetable 1980, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Item 1: System Timetable No. 16, 1980; Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Item 2: System Timetable No. 21, 1983; Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Transportation Control System 1980, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Item 1: Conductor's Instructions for TCS Work Orders, 1980; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Missouri Pacific RR. Wheel Report, Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Item 1: Instructions for the Preparation of Wheel Report Form 21015, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Union Pacific Railroad, Other Railroads, Other Organizations., Publication (Box 3)
  - Kansas City Terminal RR. Operating Rules, Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Item 1: Greater Kansas City Area, 1976; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Item 2: Operating Rules, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Item 3: Greater Kansas City Area Operating Rules, 1980; Publication (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Santa Fe RR. Operating Department Rules 1959, Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Item 1: Rules Operating Department, 1959; Publication (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - St. Louis - San Francisco RR., 1957-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 1: St. Louis-San Francisco Railway Company, 1979; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 2: Frisco Agreement between St. Louis Francisco Railway Company and System Federation No. 22 Railway Employes', 1979; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Item 3: Rules of the Transportation Department, 1957; Publication (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Union Pacific RR. Air Brakes, Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Item 1: Union Pacific System Air Brake and Train Handling Rules, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Union Pacific RR. CMS Economies, 1987; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Item 1: CMS Inquiries Time Return & Delay Report Instructions Selected TCS Inquiries, 1988; Publication (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Union Pacific RR. Hazardous Materials 1986, Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Item 1: Instructions For Handling Hazardous Materials, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Item 2: Instructions For Handling Hazardous Materials, 1983; Publication (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Union Pacific RR. Hospital Association 1957, Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Regulations, 1957; Publication (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - UTU. Info Extra, 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Info Extra (Stories about retirees, employees and their families), 2000; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Item 2: Union Pacific Railroad Company, 1954; Publication (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Union Pacific RR, Operating Rules 1953-1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Schedule of Rules Governing Wages and Working Conditions of Yardmen Represented by Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1953; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 2: General Code of Operating Rules, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Item 3: LR Johnson Jeff City, 1986; Publication (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Union Pacific RR. Safety, Radio, and General Rules 1985, Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Safety, Radio and General Rules for All Employes, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Item 2: Safety, Radio and General Rules for All Employes, 1985; Publication (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - AFL-CIO, 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: R.T.W. 14(b) Anything But., 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Item 2: Union Security: the case against the compulsory open shop, Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Item 3: the TRUTH about "Right to Work" Laws: Facts vs. Propoganda, 1977; Publication (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Association of American Railroad, 1983; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Quiz on Railroads & Railroading, 1966; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Item 2: Understanding Railroad Retirement, 1983; Publication (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Bureau of Explosives, 1955; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: Quick Reference Guide for Switching Placarded Cars, Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 2: For Trainmasters and Train and Engine Crews, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Item 3: B.E. Pamphlet 20-G For Trainmasters and Train and Engine Crews, 1955; Publication (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Fra. Federal Railroad Administration, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Hours of Service Act as Amended by Public Law 91-169, 1970; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 2: Hours of Service Act as Amended by Public Law 91-169, 1970; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 3: Hours of Service Act as Amended by Public Law 91-169, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Item 4: Track Safety Standards, 1971; Publication (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1958; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: The Power Brake Law of 1958, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 2: Railroad Safety - Long Train, 1956; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 3: The Power Brake Law of 1958, Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Item 4: WPK-s, 1956; Publication (Box 3, Folder 15)
      Author: W.H. Kennedy
  - Jefferson City Post-Tribune, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Jefferson City Post-Tribune, 1968; Publication (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Labor Magazine 1940, Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: The Labor Magazine, 1940; Publication (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Missouri State Democratic Committee, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Demo-Memo, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Missouri State Labor Council, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Are Price Controls Working?, 1972; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Item 2: Newsletter, 1973; Publication (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Missouri Operation Lifesaver Committee 1987, Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Item 1: Railroad Grade Crossing Safety - Enforcement Manual, 1981; Publication (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - NARVRE, Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 1: National Association of Retired and Veteran Railway Employees, Inc., 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Item 2: What is NARVRE, 1974; Publication (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - National Association of Railroad Passengers, Publication (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Item 1: You May Want to Take the Train but the Government, the highway lobby, and even some railroads DON'T WANT TO LET YOU. We do., 1971-1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Railroad Retirement Board 1989, Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Item 1: Furnishing Evidence to Support Your Claims, 1989; Publication (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Railway Labor Act, Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Item 1: Title 1 Definitions, 1936; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Item 2: Title 1 Definitions, 1936; Publication (Box 3, Folder 24)